Preliminary guide to the Elizabeth "Betita" Sutherland Martínez papers M1854
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- 16. Countries: travel and reference
  - Panama research, Panama articles, essays, Nacia's Latin America and Empire Report (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Panamanian sovereign documents, Vietnam trip I, Cops and robbers II (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Panama tour, Solidarity works (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Panama treaty, etc. Old Myths, New Realities (1975), John Blacken Speech, NCPS Founding conference (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - El Pais Por Conquistar la tesis del pais integral, DS Octobre 9, 1975, DS Marzo 9, 1975. DS Exclusivo, Los Agachados (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Destellos 1975, Programa de El Republico de Panama 1975, Mensaje que el excelentisimo, Senor Presidente de la republica, ing, Demetrio B. Lakas, Presenta la Asemblea Nacional de Representes de Corregimientos (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Meeting of January, 1976, Martinez J. R (Sr.) Cuba 1970's (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Vietnam research, papers, etc. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Mexico Letters, 1953 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Caribbean, Cuba (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Puerto Rico, Philosophy/Sciences, Research Memos (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Hawaii (Box 30, Folder 5, Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Africa: Global ecology (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Central America project, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Current clippings: Guatemala. Contra watch (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Current clippings: Nicaragua (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - China: Culture, songs, poems, films, teatro culture-general (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Nicaragua: obrelos y fabricas, Nica -Atlantic coast, Nica: gente vile y cordian (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Cuentos para ninos illustrated by Rini Templeton, Popular struggles- MNHE, Nica cultura, Nica agricultura (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Cartas de Cuba (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Nica book fair (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Mexico: mixed (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Mexico: unsorted (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Cuba (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Middle East: Saudi Arabia, Syria, Peace treaty, U.N socialist nations (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Middle East: Israel, Jordan, Lebenon, Palestines/PLO (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Middle East: Egypt, Iraq, Iran (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Uruguay, Mexico, CJ Revisions, Peru, Venezuela (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Mexico graphics & photos, Struggles, Cultural media (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Mexico graphics & photos, economics, peasant, farmworkers (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Mexico graphics & photos, Woman issues, Chicano-Mexicano/Latino, Mexico history, Student teacher movement, National capitalist (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Latin America: Nicaragua, Mexico (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Chile General History, Columbia (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Latin America: Bolivia, Chile, Bolivia, Ecuador & Honduras (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Latin America: Argentina, Brazil, Mexico, bananas (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Latin America: general & photos (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - South America, Latin America General (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Britain, France, Greece, Turkey, Cyprus, Ireland, Portugal, Italy, Soviet Union, Spain, Europe (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Europe General (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Panama, Nicaragua, Puerto Rico (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Guatemala, Central America U.S. involvement, Caribbean, Cuba (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Nicaragua photos, newsclippings, etc. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - EZLN Encuentro, Notebook, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - EZLN Encuentro, Mexican massacre, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - EZLN, Zapatistas, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers, Chiapas (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Zapatistas, Zapatismo 1994, EPR (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Nicaragua, Photos, Oaxaca (Box 5, Folder 7)
- 17. Books and other writing
  - Reprint of my work, End-notes (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Book-reviews, Talk re: my book, Bibliography, My acknowledgment + special note (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Fight against homelessness, Text, Launch party, Rejects, Book reviews, Promotion (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - October-November meeting 1998, Los Angeles, Procedures, Book supporters (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Distributors and media ref. (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Outline, Contracts/pix, Julia Luna Mount-extras, Women and Priesthood (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Related papers by Betita + Nancy, Comments to my sr draft (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - "The Odyssey" Betita Martinez (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Writings-Miscellaneous, Sexism and racism in textbooks, The Nation-original journals assorted, 1967-1970 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - South End Press promotion, Next printing (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Permission papers part 2. Music (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Permission papers part 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Doubleday, 1973-1974 (Flat-box 180, Folder 2)
  - Bibliography of My Work (Claudia's Project) (Box 190, Folder 18)
  - Reprints of My Work (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Position taken, Interviews of Betita (Box 140, Folder 4)
- 18. 500 Years of Chicano/Chicana History [aka Viva La Causa video]
  - 18.1 Addenda: Chicano/a Book Files part 1
    - Not to be Forgotten (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - MEChA (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Youth Credits (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Youth Page 3 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Cruz, Wash State (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Maria Berriuzabal + "Bambi" Cardenas 80's - 90's (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Chicanos/Congress (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Public Off (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - USS Forum (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - Venezuela (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - No To War (Box 182, Folder 11)
    - UN World Cont. - Racism (Box 182, Folder 12)
    - 1985 Kenya/Women UN (Box 182, Folder 13)
    - Margo Albert (Box 182, Folder 14)
    - Crafts (Arts) (Box 182, Folder 15)
    - UN. Conf. Women (Box 182, Folder 16)
    - When Native Peoples (Box 182, Folder 17)
    - Solidarity: Central America, Juarez, Cuba, Zapatistas (Box 182, Folder 18)
    - Mujer a Mujer (Box 182, Folder 19)
    - Anti-Migra, Anti 1987, Minute Men (Box 182, Folder 20)
    - 3 Leaders for Immigrants (Box 182, Folder 21)
    - AG. Wkrs, Idaho, Barrio Defense, St. Peter's, Health (Box 182, Folder 22)
    - Garment Workers, Day Labor, UFW (Box 182, Folder 23)
    - New Worker Struggle: Sneej, Swop, Fobrera, Etc. (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Ethnic Studies, Michigan, O.D.B., NM Ganados (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Film, OSA, Edu. (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Weaver's, Singers (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Radio, Artistas, Photography (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Danza Group (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Run 2004 (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Gloria Anzaldua + Cherrie (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Musicians, fingers, Misc. 1800's (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Performers: Marga Gomez (Box 183, Folder 10)
    - Denver Escuela Corky Memorial (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - Tex-Mex Singers + Accordionists (Box 183, Folder 12)
    - Early Theater (Box 183, Folder 13)
    - Lupe Briseno 1968 (Box 183, Folder 14)
    - El Chicano (Box 183, Folder 15)
    - Linda Apodaca (Box 183, Folder 16)
    - Casa-Background (Box 183, Folder 17)
    - Casa (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - ADA Sosa - Riddel (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Adeleida del Castillo (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Academics: Yolanda Broyles Gonzalez 1996 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Maria Elena Gaitan (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Monica Palacios (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Arts/Performance: Carmen Tafolla (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - Concilio Mujeres (Dorinda Moreno) (Box 184, Folder 8)
    - Houston Conf. 1971 (Box 184, Folder 9)
    - Grupo Coatlique (Box 184, Folder 10)
    - Cristina Vasquez (Box 184, Folder 11)
    - Vicki Mercado (Box 184, Folder 12)
    - Pilar Mejia (Box 184, Folder 13)
    - Black Berets (Box 184, Folder 14)
    - Idaho (Box 184, Folder 15)
    - Commision Femenil Francisca Flores (Box 184, Folder 16)
    - Priscilla + Alcon (Box 184, Folder 17)
    - Info on Lesbians + Mex. Rev. Women (Box 184, Folder 18)
    - Lesbianas (Box 184, Folder 19)
    - Native Resistance 1700's (Box 184, Folder 20)
    - PreColumbian History (Box 184, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Material (Box 184, Folder 22)
    - Unsolved Mysteries (Box 184, Folder 23)
    - Texas - Benson (Box 184, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Material (Box 184, Folder 25)
    - Teatro (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Al Norte (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Material (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Viva La Causa Pamphlet (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - 18.2 Addenda: Chicano/a Book Files part 2
    - Photographs 1930s-40s (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Viva La Causa by Judy Zalazar Drummond (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Slide Show Script (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - Slide Show on 500 Years of Chicana Womens History (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - Slides of 500 Years Chicana (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - 500 Years of Chicano History Discs 1 and 2 (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - 500 Anos De La Historia Chicana Viva La Causa (Box 185, Folder 11)
    - 450 Years of Chicano History in Pictures (Box 185, Folder 12)
    - 500 Years of Chicano History in Pictures (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - 500 Years of Chicano History in Pictures (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - 500 Years of Chicana Women's History (Box 186, Folders 3-5)
    - 500 Years of Chicana History Frame (Box 186, Item 6)
    - Viva La Causa 500 Anos de La Historia Chicana 2 VHS tapes (Box 194, Item 1)
    - Viva La Causa 500 Years of Chicano History 2 VHS tapes (Box 194, Item 2)
  - 500 years of Chicano History (Flat-box 181, Folder 3)
  - 450 anos de lucha homenaje al pueblo mexicano (Flat-box 170, Folder 2)
  - 500 Years Chicano slideshow, tapes, cassettes (Flat-box 172, Folder 1)
  - "500 years" print (Flat-box 169, Folder 1)
  - 500 years video-general, video sales (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Silva, Art, Video promo, Video-distribution, Video letterhead, Notes (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - 450 years reprint-general, 500 years letterhead, Next printing, 500 years-reviews, Mississippi letters (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Carlos M. Lessons 12/97, UC Berkeley, Extension, Spanish video Latin America, Spanish-leaflets, 500 years book orders (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - 500 years-second printing, Rutgers University Press, Misc. photos, 500 years board (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Fliers, 500 Years of Chicano History. Long leaf invoices, Book proposal 500 YCH, 500 years women order forms, Fliers, Shades guide, Rutbar catalog (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - 500 years of chicano history, Acknowledge, Publicity (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Done credits and permission: 500 years of chicana women's history (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Photo sources for 500 years chicano history (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Promo-general, Video -press packet "Cards!", Video-501-C#, Agustin Lira and musical group "Alma," Comp video, Racism-> faculty, Viva la Causa-articles, Video listings, UNM 3/8/99 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Individuals seat brochure, 500 years-attack on it-N.M. Personal-N.M. (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Promo-school teachers, Mailings, Video/promo-mailings, Video/promo catalogs, NACCS-1999 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Quotes about video, Video-promo-conferences, Women's foundations, 500 years grants/proposal, Grants-tides, Pioneer fund, Video-Grant-Resist, Correspondence, Video Grants, Misc. (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Information/permission sheet for images in Viva La Causa (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - 500 years of Chicano history, Permission form. Music documents, Houston archives (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Permissions-copies of letters sent, La gallinita roia, Videos-part II, Books: editorial strategy: Acquisitions; contacts. (part 1) (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Spanish Video photos, Historical photos (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - "500 years of Chicano History," culture, 1994-08-02 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - "500 years" Chicano video projects, Student Strike, Berets, woman, etc. (Box 52, Folders 5-6)
  - Images used in "500 years of Chicana history" (part 2). Unused images (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - "My trip to Mexico" notebook, Birthday card, Images used in "500 years of Chicana history" (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - 450 years correspondence (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - M. Bilingual 1995, McKay foundation, 500 years 1994, 450 years announcement, Photo returns, Black Oaks 1/26/92, 500 years-internal SWOP, 450 years copyright (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Changes for Spanish video, Spanish video expenses, Spanish video-permission, Promo (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Discussions, Doug, Video budget, Spanish script (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Video: Paul Robeson, UNM-Tobias Duran, SWOP, Video contract (Box 38, Folder 5)
- 19. Z, ColorLines, CrossRoads, other magazines/articles, etc.
  - My Article in Foreign Publication (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - Op Ed Mumi, 1999-10 (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - Op Ed on U.N. Conference (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - Airport Work (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Z Magazine Article on Domestic Workers, 2008 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - Z magazine, Don't Call This Country "America", 2003 (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - Articles on Latinos (Box 187, Folder 7)
  - 1st Article on Latinos, 1979-04 (Box 187, Folder 8)
  - Z #3 - New Mexico, 1989-10 (Box 187, Folder 9)
  - Z #2 (60s books) July/August, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 10)
  - Z - Mexico (2), 1989-1990 (Box 187, Folder 11)
  - Z - "Chingon Politics", 1990-04 (Box 187, Folder 12)
  - Z - "There's Move to Nov. 1990 Racism" (Box 187, Folder 13)
  - Z Article on Educ. + Racism, 1990-08 (Box 187, Folder 14)
  - Z "Tearing Down Walls on Left", 1990-09 (Box 187, Folder 15)
  - Z - "No Dogs or Mexicans", 1991-01 (Box 187, Folder 16)
  - Z - "Endangered Species", 1991-04 (Box 187, Folder 17)
  - Z - Willie Horton July/August, 1991 (Box 187, Folder 18)
  - Paper: Race, Culture, 1992 (Box 187, Folder 19)
  - Chicana Look at Z 500 Years, 1992-01 (Box 187, Folder 20)
  - Campus Racism, 1992-11 (Box 187, Folder 21)
  - Z - "Caramba, Dus Anglo Sisters...", 1992-08 (Box 187, Folder 22)
  - Z - Campus Racism, 1992-09 (Box 187, Folder 23)
  - Children's Books, 1991-12 (Box 187, Folder 24)
  - Acuna-MSS (Box 187, Folder 25)
  - Z Article Re: Women, 1992-08 (Box 187, Folder 26)
  - Univ. of Ill. Article, 1993-03 (Box 187, Folder 27)
  - Acuna Case - Extra Material (Box 187, Folder 28)
  - Fuerza Unida, 1993-01 (Box 187, Folder 29)
  - Z - Immigrants, 1993-12 (Box 187, Folder 30)
  - Cesar Chavez article, 1993-06 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Seeds of New Movimiento, 1993-09 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Raza Blowouts, 1994-11 (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Cherrie M. Book Review, 1994-02 (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - Z - Black + White, 1994-05 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - Follow Me Home (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - On Time in Missisippi, 1994-09 (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - Re-Inventing "America", 1996-12 (Box 188, Folder 9)
  - Z - Back in 1990's, 1996-12 (Box 188, Folder 10)
  - Z - Summer '97 - Terrorist War, 1997 (Box 188, Folder 11)
  - Youth: 4/22/98 Walkout, 1998 (Box 188, Folder 12)
  - Z - Network, 1998-09 (Box 188, Folder 13)
  - Z - Venceremos Brigade July/August, 1999 (Box 188, Folder 14)
  - Z - Ethnic Studies, 1999-06 (Box 188, Folder 15)
  - NYT Series, 2000-09 (Box 188, Folder 16)
  - Z - Youth Movement, 2000-05 (Box 188, Folder 17)
  - Rebels With a Cause (Box 188, Folder 18)
  - Outlaw Woman Review (Box 188, Folder 19)
  - Looking for Car (Box 188, Folder 20)
  - Looking for Color (Box 188, Folder 21)
  - Latinos Protest, 2006-06 (Box 188, Folder 22)
  - Domestic Work (Box 188, Folder 23)
  - Colorlines, Women of Color July/August, 2006 (Box 188, Folder 24)
  - Nilak Butler (Box 188, Folder 25)
  - Colorlines, 1998-2000 (Box 188, Folder 26)
  - Spain Article, 2000 (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - Beyond Chicanismo Article Fall, 2005 (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - WTO/Seattle articles, 1999-11 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - Crossroads - Activists of Color, 1991-06 (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - Crossroads Articles Miscellany, 1990-1992 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - Crossroads - Multiculturalism, 1992-05 (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - Crossroads - UCLA Victory, 1993 (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - Rascon Show, Yolanda Lopez, 1994 (Box 189, Folder 9)
  - Bobby Murray article Riverside (Box 189, Folder 10)
  - Crossroads - Breaking Borders, 1993-11 (Box 189, Folder 11)
  - Raza in Midwest (Box 189, Folder 12)
  - Notes on Net Crossroads that works (Box 189, Folder 13)
  - Crossroads - Teens Bike Barriers 12/92 - 1/93 (Box 189, Folder 14)
  - Crossroads - Women, 1993-03 (Box 189, Folder 15)
  - Crossroads - Mexico The Storm before the Storm, 1994-02 (Box 189, Folder 16)
  - Crossroads - Chiapas, 1994-05 (Box 189, Folder 17)
  - Crossroads - Walkout, 1994-09 (Box 189, Folder 18)
  - Nationalism?, 1996-07 (Box 189, Folder 19)
  - Taco Bell Cross Roads, 1995-04 (Box 189, Folder 20)
  - Book - General (Box 189, Folder 21)
  - '64 Mississippi Reunion (Box 189, Folder 23)
  - Angela Davis Article (Joint) (Box 189, Folder 24)
  - Race, Poverty & The Environment (Box 189, Folder 25)
  - Seeing More than Black and White (Box 189, Folder 26)
  - Notes for U.C. Santa Cruz Seminar, 2006-02-06 (Box 189, Folder 27)
  - White Martyrs (Book) (Box 189, Folder 28)
  - "Spy Novel" (Box 189, Folder 29)
  - Smith College - Loretta Ross Interview (Box 189, Folder 30)
  - Eyewitness Review (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - Women Building Alliances (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - WRL Book Report (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence Re: My Writings, 1980 (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - Racism in Childrens Books (C.I.B.C.) (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - Chicago "Incite", 2006-11-12 (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - Incite Article (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - Incite Articles (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - VT Press (Box 190, Folder 10)
  - Crossroads - Spanish Translating (Box 190, Folder 11)
  - Teachers 4 Social, 2006-10-14 (Box 190, Folder 12)
  - My Year of Transition, By Betita Martinez (Box 190, Folder 13)
  - Publishers (Box 190, Folder 14)
  - Article Ideas (Box 190, Folder 15)
  - "Temping" Story (Box 190, Folder 16)
  - 9/11 Thoughts by Me + Others (Box 190, Folder 17)
  - Social justice, Z magazine (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Z magazine, Against the current, ISR (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Crossroads sustainer, Promo- May 5 issues, Socialist feminist conference July 1975, A. Mex 1999-2000 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Crossroads: circulation committee, 1993-1995 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- 20. Rini Templeton- book, foundation, etc.
  Templeton, Rini
  - Rini drawings (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Prop 13-tax the corp- original high quality prints, Color originals, Betitas personal drawings by Rini (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Libros "Hospital", "El Supermercado" dibujos y textos de Rini Templeton. Solidarity/Protest. Military. Education/libraries. Vanguard foundation May Day 92 10th anniversity. Women: people meeting '81. AFW-1981. 1981 graphics (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Food processing, our co-op. Rini art Nicaragua. 1980, non-exclusive. Food. Rini-San Francisco Board of supervisors (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Rini Templeton: for publication: unused Rini Templeton: Calif y Mexico '78, Rini Templeton: Miscellanous (suelto). Rini Templeton: prop 13. Rini Templeton: Baake Y 13 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Rini Templeton: Mexico y California/78. Rini Templeton: Cuadernos y proyecto: anti-war demos (sin fecha). Rini Templeton sin titulo ni fecha cuadernos de trabajo. Rini Templeton: varios (sin titulo) (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Rini Templeton: prop 13 y otros '78. Rini Templeton: dibudos Cuba. Rini Templeton.: Libereria U.S '78. Rini Templeton: Dibulos Cuba Carnaval and folklore (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Rini Templeton: prop 13 y otros '78. Rini Templeton: dibudos Cuba. Rini Templeton.: Libereria U.S '78. Rini Templeton: Dibulos Cuba Carnaval and folklore (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Rini Templeton: cuadernos/proyecto de libro (oakland FSLN-78). Rini Templeton: Nuevo Mexico/79. Rini Templeton: Pena/ supes/ SFBMC/LOC. 315 '78. Rini Templeton: apuntos 1979 santa fe protest. Rini Templeton: Loc 315-grid lay 78. Rini Templeton: Liberia U.S Demostraciones '78 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Rini Templeton: cuadernos/proyector d libro. FSLN 78. Rini Templeton: Cuadernos/Proyectos d libro sin titulo sin fecho VIII. Rini Templeton: Mexico: frutera/ 78. Rini Templeton: cuadernos/proyector b libro oakland 78. Rini Templeton: cuaderno/proyecto d libro (oakland, 78) (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Rini Templeton: cuadernos de trabajo sin titulo (2), Rini Templeton: cuadernos de trabajo sin titulo (3), Rini Templeton Apuntos 1981 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Rini Templeton: apuntos sin fecho III, Rini Templeton apuntos sin fecho I, Rini Templeton apuntos '80 II, Rini Templeton: Cuadernos de trabajo sin titulo ni fecha, Rini Templeton: cuadernos de trabajo sin titulo 86 (1) (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Poster, Rini-S.F-Bay Area (mine), Rini: New Mexico-Mixed, Labor organizing, Health issues, Prop 13 data center, Rebel worker, N.M Review 1969-72, Valle 1977, U.S Farmworkers 1981/1983, Rini Templeton: Apuntes, sin fecho IV (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Rini Templeton Memorial Fund ledge, Shades of power (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Rini book-publisher/ distribution, Contribution-Rini book, Fund: financial reports-general Mexico 1988-finances (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Book expenses (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Rini book Mexico (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Poster ideas, Poster distributors (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Rini book: record of work, Rini Templeton Fund-paid bills (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Libro-arte de Rini Templeton, Libel problem (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Rini Templeton Memorial Fund. Capp St. money mess, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Cuba letters-uncut, Panama, Edward Bross (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Rini-writers, Cuba letters-second set (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Letters from Rini, 1968-1986 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Lat Lit #3. Rini portfolio (b16). Rini small portfolio. Sculpture correspondence. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Cards, Rini. U.S/Mexico unsorted (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Galerio De La Raza, Rini book: fiscal sponsor, Ganados del valle cards, Rini-general (non-book), Fotos de Rini, John de Puy y su padre Richard (?) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Rini notebook, murals, etc. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Rini: June-July mementos (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Real Comet contract (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Rini Templeton Memorial fund, letterhead, Capp St. Foundation (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Capp St. Foundation grant, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Expenses of Rini Templeton Memorial fund (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Rini Templeton foundation (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Release form, Rini book plans (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Rini Templeton account statement (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Rini book general correspondence, commentaries (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Pamphlets, notes, Rini Templeton (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Rini letters, Informacion para textol, Comments review/books (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Rini Book: Real Comet press (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Old versions/Healthcare (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Bibujos a incluir (banitos), Margeret Randall (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Commentaries-uncut in alphabetical order (Box 12, Folders 2-3)
  - Permissions, commentaries- leftovers (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Rini: biographical items (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Commentaries to hold for pamphlet (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Photos, sketches, Rini (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Sculptures: photos, xeroxes (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Mexico book/print sales, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - For book or Rini reviews, Rini book Arizona, Betita Martinez letter, Arizona miners (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Mary, Rini Templeton, Matt Herron Photo, Albuquerque, Sacramento exhibit (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Planta, Rini: exhibits (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Rini Book: Family (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Santa Fe prison protest, Prop 13, Rini book correspondence (Box 10, Folder 1)
- 21. Miscellaneous
  - Miscellaneous papers and newsclippings (Flat-box 181, Folder 4)
  - W/S Group, 1976 (Flat-box 180, Folder 3)
  - Plant closure expo-originals (Flat-box 179, Folder 2)
  - Key sheets (Flat-box 179, Folder 1)
  - Child plays (Flat-box 175, Folder 2)
  - Posters (Flat-box 170, Folder 3)
  - NAATA Asian film festival booklet (Flat-box 170, Folder 1)
  - Endangered species, Rini, UCSD exposed, Between the lines, Leaflet from Japan, Antonio and Rita, 1996 calenders, A peoples history (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - X-mas, Miscellaneous (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - United Nations, Betita Swarthmore, Fancy publications, "one red rose"-Rini Templeton, Oral history (Box 164, Folder 3)